جينا نعيدكن
بالعيد منسألكن
ليش ما في عنّا
لا أعياد ولا زينة؟
يا عالم أرضي محروقة...
أرضي حرية مسروقة
سمانا عم تحلم
وبتسأل الأيام:
وين الشمس الحلوة
ورفوف الحمام؟
يا عالم أرضي محروقة...
أرضي حرية مسروقة
أرضي زغيرة...
متلي زغيرة
ردولا السلام...
وأعطونا الطفولة
أعطونا الطفولة...
أعطونا أعطونا ...
أعطونا السلام
À mon enfance
À mes quatre ans
À l'innocence
Au beau jardin
À ce Liban
Qu'appellent les enfants
Je vous demande
Vous prie de rendre
Toute l'innocence
De mon enfance
Sauvez l'enfance
Sauvez Sauvez
Sauvez l'enfance...
I am a child
with something to say
Please listen to me
I am a child
who wants to play
Why don't you let me?
My doors are waiting
My friends are praying
Small hearts are begging
Give us a chance
Give us a chance...
Please! Please!
أعطونا الطفولة
أعطونا أعطونا
أعطونا السلام